<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Kashiyatra\'19</string>

    <string name="web_id">"381425729111-lu8d1rfevkdifuoeslfnldsg71ja5bdo.apps.googleusercontent.com"</string>

    <string name="app_secret" translatable="false">a23hdf348sdh34587sjhd33u98sdfh34h34g59</string>

    <string name="google_maps_key" translatable="false">AIzaSyAaxfrlsHAohnzM9Wd_FqZeAzdFZktjBAo</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="title_activity_event">EventActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_eventlist">EventListActivity</string>

    <!--    Permissions    -->
    <string name="permission_rationale_location">Access to the location service is required to show your current location on the map.</string>
    <string name="location_permission_denied">Location permission is required to show your location on map. Please try again and grant access to use the location.\nIf the permission has been permanently denied, it can be enabled from the System Settings &gt; Apps &gt; \'Kashiyatra 18\'.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="facebook_app_id" translatable="false">360998017793413</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme" translatable="false">fb360998017793413</string>

    <!--    Event Abouts    -->
    <string name="bliss_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify"><big><big><big>\"T</big></big></big>alent is not rare but the opportunity to showcase is.\" <strong>Kashiyatra</strong> unfolds to you \"<strong>Bliss</strong>-Group Dance Competition\" where synchronicity, energy and creativity unfold themselves and the stage echoes with the thud your steps, diverse with every leg yet unified with every beat.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="cut_a_rug_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify"><big><big><big>N</big></big></big>atraj is the name of Shiva that symbolizes dance: the dynamic and static divine flow of energy. It lets you dive deep into the oceans, swim without hurdles and breath freely. So loosen up yourself and go solo on the stage as <strong>Kashiyatra</strong> unveils to you \"<strong>Cut-A-Rug</strong> -Solo Dance Competition\".</p>]]></string>
    <string name="ecstasy_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify"><big><big><big>C</big></big></big>ome into an alliance with your partner and arm yourselves with all the grooves and moves, and prove it to us that you got what it takes to be a doublet for each other dancing against the world.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="cypher_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify"><big><big><big>S</big></big></big>treet dancing is the trendiest dance form today. It brings you out of the four walls into the urban streets and fills the settings with vibes that set every foot on the move!</p>]]></string>

    <string name="rangmanch_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify"><big><big><big>D</big></big></big>o you have what it takes to dissolve an audience in an ocean of emotions and actions? The colourful lights, cameras &amp; the audience are waiting for you. If you can take your expressions to the next level then this is where you belong. The stage is set and waiting for your next grand act.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="asmita_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify"><big><big><big>I</big></big></big>n civilized life, where the happiness, and indeed almost the existence, of man depends so much upon the opinion of his fellow men, he is constantly acting a studied part. In a Mono Act, an actor is totally vulnerable. His total personality is exposed to critical judgment –his intellect, his bearing, his diction, his whole appearance. If you can expose your emotions in front of the audience, here is your chance.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="hullad_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify"><big><big><big>I</big></big></big>n this fast developing world, very few people have a native taste for drama. If you can catch the attention &amp; attract people to stay and watch your performance, here is your chance. The art of grabbing the audience’s attention is all that you need. No Lights, No mics, pure ACTION full of energy.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="chestha_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify"><big><big><big>I</big></big></big>n the midst of eternal silence where slightest of the sound was finding it very difficult to escape, those creatures in the shades of black and white were making statements with their mouth stitched and were gradually paving the path for the crowd to dive deep into the sea of joyride full of laughter and emotions. Reliving those golden days when Charlie Chaplin and Marcel Marceau ruled, at Kashiyatra unfurl their hidden soul beneath you and let your mime do the chatters that won’t stop ever.</p>]]></string>

    <string name="battle_of_bands_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify"><strong><big><big><big>C</big></big></big>rosswindz</strong>, the oldest battle of bands in India, is one of the Flagship events of <strong>Kashiyatra</strong>. Since its inception, Crosswindzhas been home to major rock bands in India. Mindshift(Sweden), Tiny Fingers (Israel), Demonic Resurrection (Mumbai), Undying Inc (Delhi), Albatross (Mumbai), Underground Authority (Kolkata) have been our past headliners. Some of the past winners include Escape Artist, Diabolical Damage, High Frequency and the Purple Jays. Like the previous year, this year Crosswindz will organize a road trip for multi-city elimination rounds to ensure high quality participation from bands all over the nation leading to a tight battle to be the best.\n\tAfter the road trip selected bands will compete in the finals to be held in Varanasi. The finals will be the opening act for headliners followed by announcement of results.</p>]]></string>
    <!--<string name="instrumental_showdown_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify">Drench your soul with every piece of tone organized in a symphony and touch the real feel of music with your instruments. Get ready to rock the stage with skills and innovate your talents.</p>]]></string>-->

    <string name="sur_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify"><big><big><big>\"M</big></big></big>usic touches us emotionally, where words alone can’t.\" So if you have the voice that can win hearts and steal the show, then get ready to dazzle the stage as we bring forth <strong>Sur</strong>, where you are given the ideal platform to show your talent and prove your mettle.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="raagsamar_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify"><big><big><big>I</big></big></big>f you think you can enthral the audience by singing on soft acoustic music if unplugged tunes are all you need to set the cool vibes around then don\'t miss the chance to participate in Unplugged!</p>]]></string>
    <string name="sanlayan_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify"><big><big><big>T</big></big></big>here\'s something in the soft plink of a sitar, or the mellifluous notes of a flute, that the human voice cannot seem to match. Instrumentalists spend years perfecting their art, to achieve the thrilling pace at which they change notes. <strong>Kashiyatra</strong> gives you a chance for you to hear and create magic-harmonies with instruments only. Let your emotions radiate and shine in its own character through instruments. <strong>Sanlayan</strong> is the solo instrumental music competition.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="kriti_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify"><strong><big><big><big>K</big></big></big>riti</strong> is your chance to let your imagination and creativity flow in the form of a beautiful self-composed song. Stand out as that brilliantly clear soloist as you take control over the vocals and mesmerize the audience. This is awarded to the performer who presents the best and wins the hearts with their creation.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="advaita_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify"><big><big><big>I</big></big></big>f you think you can make the crowd forget themselves in your performance, then this is the place to be. <strong>Advaita</strong> is undoubtedly the most popular event of <strong>Bandish</strong>. With massive enthusiasm and fearsome competition, this event brings out the best in its participants striving for glory. If you have the band that just can’t lose and have hunger for more, then come and perform against the most formidable bands in India. It is the battle of bands, and the clash is raging hotter than ever.</p>]]></string>

    <string name="design_elegante_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify"><big><big><big>\'M</big></big></big>IRAGE\' -An illusion that bounds every viewer with the ethereal beauty. <strong>Mirage</strong> gives you an opportunity to bring out the creative designer in you to change the fashion statement of India. Wear your designer hats, pick your magic brushes, design and present your collection of dresses at <strong>Kashiyatra \'18</strong>, centered on incredible themes and get an opportunity to win hefty prizes.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="mr_ky_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify"><big><big><big>W</big></big></big>hile going outdoors everyone likes to pull out the best of them with a secret dream of being Mr. India or Mr. Universe someday . So it\'s time to sizzle things up. It\'s time for <strong>Mr. KY</strong> a step leading you closer to your dream. An unrivaled opportunity to be the defining personality. If you think you have it in you to stand out from the crowd and clinch this coveted title, participate now and leave an everlasting impression on the mind of every attendant of KY!</p>]]></string>
    <string name="miss_ky_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify"><big><big><big>\"T</big></big></big>he stage sets on fire, when the unseen, unforgettable, ultimate accessory and perception of fashion heralds the arrival of blistering and dynamic girls of this country which finally lead to their charismatic departure.\" <strong>Kashiyatra</strong> brings to you all. an opportunity to turn your dreams into reality.\n\tLet truth be told -each one of us, at some point in our lives, has spent hours in front of mirrors, wishing to be the Miss India or Miss universe. We bring to you a competition that could be a step in fulfilling your dreams, <strong>Miss KY</strong>.</p>]]></string>

    <string name="rapid_fire_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify"><big><big><big>\"T</big></big></big>he trouble is you think you have time\" -Buddha. Well, you don\'t! This contest pitches your creativity against the cruel boundaries of time. We decide the rules of the game. We decide when the bell rings. But it\'s only you who sets the limits of your imagination and creativity.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="spoil_the_tees_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify"><big><big><big>\"D</big></big></big>aag achche hote hain\" Get those spotless white T-Shirts and spoil them. Yeah, you heard it right, put colour on them, soil them, and spoil them. Use paints. Use brushes. Use your hands. It doesn\'t matter. Just funk them up. Add life to those boring whites. Coz life is too short for boring T-Shirts!</p>]]></string>
    <string name="vastra_shilp_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify"><big><big><big>\"F</big></big></big>ashion is art and you are the canvas\"-Velvet Paper. So, wake up the Coco Chanel inside you and let your creativity do the talking. Weave out art and style with the fabrics of your imagination and yeah-paper.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="rangbaazi_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify"><big><big><big>\"A</big></big></big>rt is the only way to run away without leaving home\" and \"Colours are the best form of expression\". Wouldn\'t you agree? Show us your creativity by using brushes, toothbrushes your fingers etc. to paint but without using a pencil to sketch. Can you beat the twist?</p>]]></string>
    <string name="face_painting_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify"><big><big><big>E</big></big></big>ver thought about art in a quirky way? That it is not always a serious issue of expression of emotions but a way to have fun? If yes, then paint your buddy\'s face on the given theme to nick prizes away!</p>]]></string>
    <string name="soap_carving_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify"><big><big><big>\"I</big></big></big>saw the angel in the marble and carved until I set him free.\" -Michelangelo\n\tThough carving a stone is tough, what\'s easy is carving soap. And that\'s why we give you the \"soap\". Just carve your creativity out on these mundane pieces of soap and transform them into pieces of art.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="ink_it_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify"><big><big><big>D</big></big></big>esign a unique tattoo with some amazing ideas, artwork and style. Get ready to define the concept of body art!</p>]]></string>

    <string name="india_quiz_about"><![CDATA[<style>p{text-align:justify}</style><p><big><big><big>A</big></big></big> total of Six intriguing quizzes are organised by the IIT BHU Quiz Club during <strong>Kashiyatra 2018</strong> namely:</p><ul><li>India Quiz (No entry fee)</li><li>MELA (Music Entertainment Literature Arts)</li><li>General Quiz</li><li>Sports Quiz</li><li>Biz Tech Quiz</li><li>TLC(Travel, Living and Culture) Quiz</li></ul></p>]]></string>
    <string name="mela_about">@string/india_quiz_about</string>
    <string name="general_quiz_about">@string/india_quiz_about</string>
    <string name="sports_quiz_about">@string/india_quiz_about</string>
    <string name="biz_tech_about">@string/india_quiz_about</string>
    <string name="tlc_about">@string/india_quiz_about</string>

    <string name="scripturesque_about"><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify"><big><big><big>\"W</big></big></big>itness the Oeuvres of Lord L’oquent\"- History has shown that those who influence all others with words always reign supreme. Yet, so often, these souls challenge each other to test the sharpness of their tongues and the genius of their minds. Such conflicts result in the most devastating of all battles, a battle of ideas, a clashing of principles. Ascend to the halls of Valhalla through your wit and oratory abilities. Challenge Cicero himself at the podium and prove once and for all that none stand above you in grand old art of using words to sway minds.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="battlefront_about">@string/scripturesque_about</string>
    <string name="shipwreck_cove_about">@string/scripturesque_about</string>
    <string name="the_legend_of_sir_speak_a_lot_about">@string/scripturesque_about</string>
    <string name="a_jesters_court_about">@string/scripturesque_about</string>
    <string name="vaad_vivaad_about">@string/scripturesque_about</string>
    <string name="alfaaz_about">@string/scripturesque_about</string>
    <string name="ashubhashan_about">@string/scripturesque_about</string>
    <string name="whats_the_word_about">@string/scripturesque_about</string>
    <string name="hinkhoj_about">@string/scripturesque_about</string>

    <!--    Event Short Descriptions    -->
    <string name="bliss_short_description">Group Dance</string>
    <string name="cut_a_rug_short_description">Solo Dance</string>
    <string name="ecstasy_short_description">Duet Dance</string>
    <string name="cypher_short_description">Street Dance</string>
    <string name="rangmanch_short_description">Stage Play</string>
    <string name="asmita_short_description">Mono Act</string>
    <string name="hullad_short_description">Street Play</string>
    <string name="chestha_short_description">Mime</string>

    <string name="battle_of_bands_short_description">Battle of Bands</string>
    <!--<string name="instrumental_showdown_short_description"></string>-->
    <string name="sur_short_description">Solo Singing</string>
    <string name="raagsamar_short_description">Accoustic Unplugged Singing</string>
    <string name="sanlayan_short_description">Solo Instrumental</string>
    <string name="kriti_short_description">Original Composition</string>
    <string name="advaita_short_description">Indie Rock Band </string>
    <string name="design_elegante_short_description"></string>
    <string name="mr_ky_short_description"></string>
    <string name="miss_ky_short_description"></string>
    <string name="rapid_fire_short_description">Art Marathon</string>
    <string name="spoil_the_tees_short_description">T-shirt art Competition</string>
    <string name="vastra_shilp_short_description">Paper Costume Designing</string>
    <string name="rangbaazi_short_description">Painting with a Twist</string>
    <string name="face_painting_short_description">Paint Face</string>
    <string name="soap_carving_short_description">Soap Carving </string>
    <string name="ink_it_short_description">Tattoo Making</string>
    <string name="india_quiz_short_description">Quiz Competition</string>
    <string name="mela_short_description">@string/india_quiz_short_description</string>
    <string name="general_quiz_short_description">@string/india_quiz_short_description</string>
    <string name="sports_quiz_short_description">@string/india_quiz_short_description</string>
    <string name="biz_tech_short_description">@string/india_quiz_short_description</string>
    <string name="scripturesque_short_description">Creative Writing</string>
    <string name="battlefront_short_description">English Debate</string>
    <string name="shipwreck_cove_short_description">English Extempore</string>
    <string name="the_legend_of_sir_speak_a_lot_short_description">English Elocution-cum-poetry-slam</string>
    <string name="a_jesters_court_short_description">Stand-up Comedy</string>
    <string name="vaad_vivaad_short_description">Hindi Debate</string>
    <string name="alfaaz_short_description">Hindi Elocution-cum-Poetry-Slam</string>
    <string name="ashubhashan_short_description">Hindi Extempore</string>
    <string name="whats_the_word_short_description">Word Games</string>
    <string name="hinkhoj_short_description">Hindi Word Games</string>


    <!--    Event Rules    -->
    <string name="bliss_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><h4>PRELIMINARY ROUND</h4><p><u>Time Limit</u>: 3-5 minutes. Exceeding this will lead to penalization in marks.</p><p><u>Team Size</u>: Minimum of 5 and maximum of 35 members are allowed in a team, with at least 3 and at most 20 members on stage at any point during the performance.</p><ol><li>All dance forms except folk are allowed.</li><li>Participants can use props suited to their performance. Props which might cause inconvenience to the other teams or cause damage to the stage or the surroundings, will not be entertained under any circumstance (this applies to any kind of fluid, flame, powders, colours, confetti, glass etc.).</li><li>The performance must be a part of the routine that is to be presented in the final round.</li><li> Participants are required to give the corresponding edited audio songs of both the rounds in .mp3 format, in PENDRIVES ONLY and must be submitted at the time of registration. Other devices such as CDs or mobile phones etc. will not be accepted.</li><li>Decision of the judges and the coordinators will be considered as final and binding and will not be changed under any circumstances.</li><li>Obscenity of any kind will lead to immediate disqualification.</li></ol><h4>FINAL ROUND</h4><p><u>Stage setting time</u>: 2 minutes (maximum).</p><p><u>Time Limit</u>: 6-10 minutes. Exceeding this will lead to penalization in marks.<ol><li>Participants can use props suited to their performance.</li><li>Participants are required to give the corresponding edited audio songs in .mp3 format, in PENDRIVES ONLY along with the final round track and must be submitted at the time of registration.</li><li>No substitutions are allowed. The same team that was registered for the eliminations only will be allowed to perform in the finals if it qualifies.</li><li>Any specific requirements regarding lights and smoke must be discussed with organizers well in advance.</li></ol><p>[NOTE: The pendrive must contain two tracks, one for preliminary round and the other for final. Named as: BLISS –your group name/college name-round(PRELIMS/FINAL), e.g.: BLISS-IITBHU-PRELIMS indicates IITBHU’s track for PRELIMINARY round].</p>]]></string>
    <string name="cut_a_rug_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><ol><li>All dance forms are allowed.</li><li>There will be three rounds present in the competition.</li><li>In the first round, participants will perform for not more than 1 minute. The performance must be a part of the routine that is to be presented in the second round.</li><li>In the second round, participants will have 4 minutes (maximum) to perform.</li><li>The final round will be a one-on-one face-off competition in which the finalists will perform on the spot to a music piece selected randomly which will be given to the participant 5 minutes before their performance.</li><li>Participants can use props suited to their performance. Use of any kind of fluid, flame, powders, glass and colours is not allowed.</li><li>Participants are required to give the corresponding edited audio songs in .mp3 format, in PENDRIVES ONLY along and must be submitted at the time of registration. Other devices such as CDs or mobile phones etc. will not be accepted.</li><li>Decision of the judges and the coordinators will be considered as final and binding and will not be changed under any circumstance.</li></ol><p>[NOTE: The pendrive must contain two tracks, one for first round and the other for second. Named as: CAR-your_name-round_name(PRELIMS/FINAL)\ne.g.: CAR-P_Ashutosh-PRELIMS indicates P.Ashutosh’s track for PRELIMINARY round].</p>]]></string>
    <string name="ecstasy_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><h4>PRELIMINARY ROUND</h4><p><u>Time Limit</u>: 2 minutes. Exceeding this will lead to penalization in marks.</p><ol><li>All dance forms allowed.</li><li>There is no gender restriction.</li><li>Participants can use props suited to their performance. Props which might cause inconvenience to the other teams or cause damage to the stage or the surroundings, will not be entertained under any circumstance (this applies to any kind of fluid, flame, powders, colours, confetti, glass etc.).</li><li>Participants are required to give the corresponding edited audio songs of both the rounds in .mp3 format, in PENDRIVES ONLY and must be submitted at the time of registration.</li><li>Decision of the judges and the coordinators will be considered as final and binding and will not be changed under any circumstances.</li></ol><h4>FINAL ROUND</h4><p><u>Time Limit</u>: 5 minutes. Exceeding this will lead to penalization in marks.</p><ol><li>Use of water, fire and glass is prohibited.</li><li>Participants are required to give the corresponding edited audio songs of both the rounds in .mp3 format, in PENDRIVES ONLY and must be submitted at the time of registration.</li><li>Any specific requirements regarding lights and smoke must be discussed with organizers well in advance.</li></ol><p>[NOTE: The pendrive must contain two tracks, one for preliminary round &amp; the other for final. Named: ECS -participants_name-round (PRELIMS/ FINAL),<br>e.g.: ECS-John, Jane-FINAL indicates John &amp; Jane’s track for FINAL round].</p>]]></string>
    <string name="cypher_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><ol><li>Minimum 5 and maximum 10 dancers per team.</li><li>All the participating teams should send a playlist containing five songs on which they would like to perform in the street dance faceoff.</li><li>These playlists once collected from all the participating teams will be shuffled entirely and played at random for the faceoff.</li><li>The faceoff can have a solo dancer, duo or the entire team.</li><li>There will be only knockout rounds. The last two best teams remaining will faceoff for the winner position.</li><li>Teams should bring their portable music systems for practice.</li><li>The dance floor area must be in the same condition after the performances as before.</li><li>No props will be provided.</li><li>Individuality and originality of the dance are encouraged as well as interaction and contact with the spectators and the other dancers.</li><li>Dancers are not restricted from performing any move,but they must be aware that it is their responsibility to ensure that they do not perform criticalsteps that could injure themselves or others. Coordinators have the right to bring in safety restrictions.</li></ol>]]></string>
    <string name="rangmanch_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><ol><li>Length of the play should be around 20 to 50 minutes, with a penalty for every extra minute. An extra time of 5 minutes will be given both for setting as well as clearing the stage.</li><li>A technical check (both lights and sound) will be provided to each team before the starting of the event.</li><li>The play could be in English, Hindi or Bilingual. Short phrases of other languages can be used.</li><li>There is no restriction to team size.</li><li>Teams are allowed to have one member each for lights, sound and spot. In addition to that a maximum of three backstage helpers are allowed. Their names should be mentioned separately at the time of Registration.</li><li>Any Inappropriate content or vulgarity will not be tolerated.</li><li>Spillage of any item is strictly not allowed on stage.</li><li>The decision of the organizers shall be final and abiding.</li><li>Slot preference will be given in the order of registration on the first come first serve basis.</li></ol>]]></string>
    <string name="chestha_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><ol><li>Team Limit: 8+2 persons</li><li>Time Limit: 10minutes</li><li>Unnecessary use of props is discouraged.</li><li>Face painting and costumes would not be considered as a prop.</li><li>The act should not contain any dialogues, lip syncs.</li><li>Background music is allowed. However, it must not contain any words (sound representing any living form is not allowed).</li><li>The decision of judges will be final and binding.</li><li>Any fluid/flame is not allowed.</li><li>No act shall contain any obscene, disrespectful actions or gestures. The act will immediately be stopped,and entry will be disqualified if these instructions are not followed.</li></ol>]]></string>
    <string name="asmita_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><ol><li>A participant can have a maximum of 3 helpers, one each for lights and sound and the third one could be incorporated in the act as per need.</li><li>The act can be in English, Hindi or Bilingual. Short phrases of other languages can be used.</li><li>Time Limit: 4-10 minutes.</li><li>Any fluid, live animals, flames, heavy objects or any material which has a possibility of damaging the stage is not allowed.</li><li>Spillage of any item is strictly not allowed on stage.</li><li>Points will be deducted on exceeding the time limit.</li><li>Any Inappropriate content or vulgarity will not be tolerated.</li><li>The decision of the judges and organizers shall be final and abiding.</li></ol> ]]></string>
    <string name="hullad_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><ol><li><u>Team Size</u>: 10-30 (including CAs &amp; music accompanists)</li><li>Teams have to mail the following things at events.kashiyatra@gmail.com: Synopsis of the play (not more than 100 words) and Prod List (List of production material and music instruments brought by the teams). The subject of the email should be \"College Name_PlayName\" before the mentioned deadline.</li><li>Time Limit: 15-30 minutes. Points will be deducted on exceeding the time limit.</li><li>Judging Criteria: Acting, Voice (Sync, modulation and diction) Screenplay, Script, Audience Interaction &amp; overall impact.</li><li>The Team size represents the number of people registered as a team. Only these shall be allowed to perform the Street play.</li><li>Music accompanists are included in the team number stated above. Maximum of 4 can be included in the team.</li><li>Teams are expected to perform at an open air venue with audience all around.</li><li>No electrical appliances shall be allowed during the performance whether inside or outside the circle of performance.</li><li>Only live music is allowed. Teams will have to bring their own instruments-no instruments will be provided.</li><li>The language of the performance should be Hindi/English or both. However, short sub passages in other languages are allowed.</li><li>Any fluid, live animals, flames, heavy objects or any material which has a possibility of damaging the stage is not allowed.</li><li>Dry colours may be used during the play, but the teams have to clean the stage after their performance &amp; the cleaning time will be included in the performance time.</li><li>Any plagiarism &amp; profanity will lead to immediate disqualification.</li><li>The decision of the judges and organizers will be final &amp; abiding.</li></ol>]]></string>
    <string name="battle_of_bands_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><p>The competition will be held in two phases, zonals in various cities and the finals in Varanasi.</p><h4>Zonals (subject to change as per venue)</h4><ol><li>The competition is open to all English semi-professional bands.</li><li>Each band would be given a playing time of 25 minutes, inclusive of sound set-up.</li><li>Basic sound equipment and a standard drum-kit will be provided; bands are however advised to bring their guitars, keyboards, and additional equipment.</li><li>There is no upper limit for the number of members in a band, however, at any point in time, at least three members need to be on the stage.</li><li>No pre-recorded audio or MIDI interfaces are allowed. However, bands can use looper pedals for live loopings.</li><li>All songs much have their lyrics written in English.</li><li>The judge’s decision will be final.</li><li>Based on the participation, we will select a maximum of two bands who will advance for the finals in Varanasi.(we can choose more bands on the particular recommendation of judges)</li></ol><h4>Finals</h4><ol><li>Every band should have at least one original composition.</li><li>Varanasi zonals will be held during Kashiyatra. The bands which have already participated in any other zonals can also participate in the Varanasi Zonals.</li><li>The finals will be held in Varanasi during Kashiyatra. All the bands have to arrange their travel up to Varanasi.</li><li>Bands will be given 15 minutes time before their performances for sound setup. They can save the patches at that moment for their performances.</li><li>The performance time is limited to 20 minutes per band. The performances will be right before the headlining act by Guest Bands.</li><li>No pre-recorded audio or MIDI interfaces are allowed. However bands can use looperpedals for live loopings.</li><li>All songs much have their lyrics written in English.</li><li>The judge’s decision will be final, the results would be announced by the judges right after the headlining act of that day.</li><li> Any change in the above rules will be notified to the concerned bands prior to their performances.</li></ol>]]></string>
    <!--<string name="instrumental_showdown_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><p>The event is open for instrumentalists who want to show their improvisation skills.<h4>Rules for prelims:</h4><ol><li>Instrumentalists would be given a time of 6 minutes each to show their skills. They are expected to utilise the time to showcase their technical skills and ability to improvise.</li><li>Allowed instruments are Guitars, Bass, Keyboards and any other non-percussive instrument.<br>Note: Participants are required to bring their instruments.</li><li>No pre-recorded audio is allowed, however live looping can be done.</li><li>Instrumentalists are encouraged to play original compositions.</li><li>Decision of the judge and coordinators will be final.</li></ol><h4>Rules for finals:</h4><ol><li>Based on their performance in the prelims, instrumentalists would be shortlisted based on their instruments.</li><li>In consultation with the judge, we will release a few backing tracks and players will judged on their live improvisation of these.</li><li>The tracks will be notified to the players a few hours before the event, and they will need to choose their preferred one.</li><li>Decision of the judge and coordinators will be final.]]></string>-->
    <string name="sur_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><ol><li>Time Limit:<ol type="a"><li>Elimination- 3 minutes including sound-check.</li><li>Prelims- 4 minutes including sound-check.</li><li>Finale- 6 minutes including sound-check.</li></ol></li><li>Genre: Classical songs are NOT allowed. However, Semi-classical, Light Indian Music, Bollywood and Western songs (NO screaming/growling) are permitted.</li><li>Language: All languages are allowed.</li><li>Background tracks are permitted. Participants will have to carry it in a pendrive and the submission of the track should be done before the event.</li><li>You may be asked to sing another song on judge’s demand.</li><li>Mashups and Medleys are allowed, provided they don’t exceed the time limit.</li><li>You may bring along two accompanying instrumentalists with you, or may play the instrument yourself, or use an Electronic Tanpura(under either case, you can’t use more than two instruments.). Only vocals shall be judged, however.</li><li>Judging Criteria: Voice Quality, Voice Modulation, Sur, Taal and Choice of Song.</li><li>Points may be deducted on exceeding the time limit.</li><li>You have to perform a different composition in each round of the event.</li><li>The decision of the judges and the organizers will be final &amp; abiding.</li></ol>]]></string>
    <string name="raagsamar_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><ol><li>A 3- piece drum kit and a bass guitar will be provided to the participants and instrument other than those will have to arrange by the participant on their own.</li><li>The team must have a minimum of 3 members and a maximum often members.</li><li>The participant should use at least one melodic instrument in the performance.</li><li>No electric guitars are allowed, and only piano and strings patches are permitted on Synth.</li><li>The performance can have a medley of songs, a cover and a group song. No pre-mixed voices of samples are allowed.</li><li>Time limit for the performance is 12 min (including sound check).</li><li>The decision of the judges will be final.</li></ol>]]></string>
    <string name="sanlayan_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><h4>Preliminary Round</h4><ol><li>Time limit: 6 minutes including sound check.</li><li>Genre: All genres are accepted.</li><li>Backing tracks are not allowed but music can be looped in real time.</li><li>Judging Criteria: Clarity of Rendition, Creativity, Proficiency and level of difficulty of composition. Original pieces will be given due points.</li><li>Points may be deducted on exceeding the time limit or in case of using the aid of written notations.</li><li>All Instruments (String, Wind, Percussion-Electronic as well as Acoustic) are allowed.</li><li>The participants will be judged in 2 separate categories : <br>Percussion and non percussion.</li><li>The decision of the judges and the organizers will be final &amp; abiding.</li></ol><h4>Final Round</h4><ol><li>Selected participants from the prelims will go into the final round.</li><li>General rules will remain same as the prelims.</li><li>In the final round, for the percussion category, each selected participant will be given a melody/baseline on the spot, to play on.</li><li>For the non-percussion category, each selected participant will be given a drum beat on the spot, to play on.</li><li>All the participants are required to play and improvise on the given track.</li><li>The decision of the judges and the organizers will be final &amp; abiding.</li></ol>]]></string>
    <string name="kriti_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><ol><li>Time Limit: 10 minutes (including sound check)</li><li>You can perform only one composition.</li><li>Your song should be self-written and self-composed.</li><li>Screaming and growling are not allowed.</li><li>Your song can be a pure instrumental composition however song with lyrics will be preferred.</li><li>You can repeat the same composition performed in Kriti as in any of the other events of the Bandish.</li><li>If your song contains lyrics printed copies of the same should be brought at the time of the event.</li><li>Judging Criteria: Originality of ideas, Creativity, Composition, Arrangement of the song, Sur, Lyrical Content, Taaland Voice quality.</li><li>Plagiarism of any kind will be detrimental to one’s score.</li><li>Point may be deducted on exceeding the time limit or in case of not memorizing the lyrics (Vocalisits) or using written notations (Instrumentalists).</li><li>The decision of the judges and the organizers will be final &amp; abiding.</li></ol>]]></string>
    <string name="advaita_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><ol><li>Time Limit: 25 minutes including sound check.</li><li>Your performance may be of any genre and language.</li><li>Mashups and Medleys are allowed, provided they don’t exceed the time limit.</li><li>Genre: Classical songs are NOT allowed. However, Semi-classical, Light Indian Music, Bollywood and Western songs (NO screaming/ growling) are permitted.</li><li>Band members should not fall below 3 and should not exceed 10.</li><li>Obscenity and vulgarity are not allowed in lyrics and gestures.</li><li>No pre-recorded music is allowed although music can be looped in real time.</li><li>We only provide the five-piece drum set; any further instruments should be arranged by the participants only.</li><li>For preliminary round, you have to mail your video to events.kashiyatra@gmail.com with the video renamed as “ADVAITA-Band_name”.</li><li>You have to submit the lyrics printed copy at the time of the event.</li><li>Judging Criteria: Instrumental Brilliance, Creativity, Stage Presence, Tightness, Vocals and Public Appeal.</li><li>Points may be deducted on exceeding the time limit or in case of not memorising the lyrics (vocalists) or using the aid of written notations (instrumentalists).</li><li>The decision of the judges and the organisers will be final & abiding.</li></ol>]]></string>
    <string name="design_elegante_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul {padding-left:16px}</style><ol style="text-align:justify"><li>There is no limit on the number of designers in the team. They are supposed to represent their designs through models.</li><li>A team should consist of a minimum of 8 models (apart from designers). The team members can be from the same or a different institution.</li><li>Each team will have to choose a theme and costumes/dresses should be centred on the selected theme. There is no restriction on the theme* and you can freely make use of any means to choose one.<u>Here are some suggestions</u>: Any Indian Mythology (Maheshmati, Bajirao Mastani, Jodha Akbar), Recycling, Mismatch, Animals in Cage, Ethnic, Shahi Libaaz, Being Banarasi.</li><li>The participating teams will have to get themselves registered for participation either online or through Campus Ambassador of your college.</li><li>Participating teams will have to submit a written document which should contain a summary of the theme elaborating the relation of their dress collection to the chosen theme, formation and music for a walk, prior to the event. Email your document to events.kashiyatra@gmail.com.</li><li>There will be two rounds - Prelims and Finals.</li><li><strong>For prelims:</strong>Each team will be allotted a time slot of 4-6 minutes for the onstage performance. Exceeding the time will lead to penalisation.</li><li><strong>For finals:</strong>Each team will be allotted a time slot of maximum 8 minutes for the onstage performance. Exceeding the time will lead to penalisation.</li><li>Teams are suggested to inform the organisers of any props they are planning to use. Use of water, fire, pets or any hazardous materials is not allowed. Teams are instructed to consult with the organisers before using any such material.</li><li>Teams will have to bring their music for the walk in the pen-drive and submit it at least 30 minutes prior to the event. </li><li>The teams will be judged on the following basis:<ul><li>Theme</li><li>Design of the Dress</li><li>Walk</li><li>Music</li><li>Formation on the stage</li><li>Written document submitted at the time of registration</li></ul></li><li>Failure in portraying the chosen theme will lead to negative points.</li><li>The decision of the judges will be final & abiding.</li><li>The obscenity of any kind is not allowed and will lead to immediate disqualification.</li></ol>]]></string>
    <string name="mr_ky_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><h3>Preliminary Round</h3><ul><li>The participants need to showcase their talent by carrying their dresses elegantly and walking just like a King on the red carpet.</li><li>Individuals are free to choose the style of their outfits.</li><li>After the walk, participants have to give their introduction.</li><li>Judging criteria:  Walk, Dress and Personality.</li><li>The decision of the judges and organisers will be final & abiding.</li><li>The obscenity of any kind is not allowed and will lead to immediate disqualification.</li></ul><h3>Final Round</h3><ul><li>The participants need to showcase their talent by carrying their dresses elegantly and walking just like a King.</li><li>There is a Questionnaire Round. The participants would need to impress the judges with out of the box answers to their questions.</li><li>Participants will be judged on their ability to project their personality and project his views</li><li>The decision of the judges and organisers will be final & abiding.</li><li>The obscenity of any kind is not allowed and will lead to immediate disqualification.</li></ul>]]></string>
    <string name="miss_ky_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><h3>Preliminary Round</h3><ul><li>The participants need to showcase their talent by carrying their dresses elegantly and walking just like a Queen on the red carpet.</li><li>Individuals are free to choose the style of their outfits.</li><li>After the walk, participants have to give their introduction.</li><li>Judging criteria:  Walk, Dress and Personality.</li><li>The decision of the judges and organisers will be final & abiding.</li><li>The obscenity of any kind is not allowed and will lead to immediate disqualification.</li></ul><h3>Final Round</h3><ul><li>The participants need to showcase their talent by carrying their dresses elegantly and walking just like a Queen.</li><li>There is a Questionnaire Round. The participants would need to impress the judges with out of the box answers to their questions.</li><li>Participants will be judged on their ability to project their personality and project his views</li><li>The decision of the judges and organisers will be final & abiding.</li><li>The obscenity of any kind is not allowed and will lead to immediate disqualification.</li></ul>]]></string>
    <string name="rapid_fire_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><p><u>Time Limit</u>: 4 hours</p><ol><li>Three contests to be completed within given time frame.</li><li>The contests and time limit to be declared on the spot.</li><li>Participants need to participate in teams of four.</li><li>All materials will be provided on the spot.</li><li>Judging Criteria: Creativity, Neatness, Relevance to the theme, Artistic skills and Overall appeal.</li><li>The decision of the judges will be final &amp; abiding.]]></string>
    <string name="spoil_the_tees_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><p><u>Time Limit</u>: 3 hours</p><ol><li>Teams of maximum three members.</li><li>The theme will be given on the spot.</li><li>Fabric colour, T-shirts, brushes, etc. will be provided.</li><li>No additional materials are allowed.</li><li>Judging Criteria: Creativity, Relevance to the theme, Wear-ability, Visual appeal.</li><li>The decision of the judges will be final &amp; abiding.</li></ol>]]></string>
    <string name="vastra_shilp_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><p><u>Time Limit</u>: 3 hours</p><ol><li>Teams of maximum four members.</li><li>The theme will be given on the spot.</li><li>All the relevant materials (coloured sheets, Fevicol, etc.) will be provided.</li><li>No other material is allowed.</li><li>Judging Criteria: Creativity, Relevance to the theme, Uniqueness, Finishing, Style.</li><li>The decision of the judges will be final &amp; abiding.</li></ol>]]></string>
    <string name="rangbaazi_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><p><u>Time Limit</u>: 2 Hours.</p><ol><li>Teams of maximum two members.</li><li>Theme will be given on the spot.</li><li>A4 sheets, poster colours and relevant materials will be provided on the spot.</li><li>No other material is allowed.</li><li>Judging criteria: Creativity, relevance to the theme, uniqueness.</li><li>The decision of judges will be final and abiding.</li></ol>]]></string>
    <string name="face_painting_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><p><u>Time Limit</u>: 2 hours</p><ol><li>A team of maximum two members.</li><li>All materials to be provided on spot.</li><li>A4 sheet, poster colours, tissue paper, brushes ad relevant materials will be provided. No external materials are allowed</li><li>Judging Criteria: Creativity, uniqueness, relevance to the theme.</li><li>The decision of the judges will be final &amp; abiding.</li></ol>]]></string>
    <string name="soap_carving_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><p><u>Time Limit</u>: 3 hours</p><ol><li>Teams of maximum two members.</li><li>Theme will be given on the spot.</li><li>Cutters, Soap, Fevicol, etc. will be provided.</li><li>No additional materials are allowed.</li><li>Judging Criteria: Creativity, Carving skills, Complexity of design, Representation of the theme.</li><li>The decision of the judges will be final &amp; abiding.</li></ol>]]></string>
    <string name="ink_it_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><p><u>Time Limit</u>: 2 hours.</p><ol><li>Team of maximum 2 members.</li><li>A4 sheets, sketch pens, paints, brushes, etc will be provided.</li><li>No additional materials are allowed.</li><li>The decision of organisers will be final and abiding.</li></ol>]]></string>
    <string name="india_quiz_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><ol><li>Each team will have a maximum of 3 members.</li><li>The event will take place in two rounds, prelims followed by the finals.</li><li>All the team members of a team must be from the same college.</li><li>8 teams from the prelims will qualify for the finals.</li><li>In the finals, the quiz master will explain detailed rules before conducting every round.</li><li>Use of any unfair means is strictly prohibited and will lead to immediate disqualification.</li><li>The quiz master\'s decision is final and abiding.</li></ol>]]></string>
    <string name="mela_rules">@string/india_quiz_rules</string>
    <string name="general_quiz_rules">@string/india_quiz_rules</string>
    <string name="sports_quiz_rules">@string/india_quiz_rules</string>
    <string name="biz_tech_rules">@string/india_quiz_rules</string>
    <string name="scripturesque_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><ol><li>There\'ll be four sub-events under this—English Poetry Writing, English Prose Writing, Hindi Poetry Writing, and Hindi Prose Writing.</li><li>Topics will be given on the spot and 1.5 hour writing time is given.</li><li>Judging criteria include creativity, style, and relevance to the topic.</li><li>All the sub-events will be judged separately.</li><li>Any plagiarism will result in disqualification.</li><li>The decision of the judges is final.</li></ol>]]></string>
    <string name="battlefront_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><h4>Preliminary Round</h4><p><u>Style: Turncoat</u></p><ol><li>It is an extempore event, so the topics will be provided on the spot and each participant shall be given TWO minutes to prepare.</li><li>The participants shall have to argue both sides of the topic themselves, that is, they would be speaking both FOR and AGAINST the motion.</li><li>The participants shall first speak FOR the motion of the house for TWO MINUTES, and then SWITCH their stance to AGAINST the motion and speak for another TWO MINUTES.</li><li>The remaining time from one segment can\'t carry over to the other.</li><li>The decision of the judges is final and profanity will be penalized with disqualification.</li></ol><h4>Final Round</h4><p><u>Style: British Parliamentary</u></p><ol><li>Following the prelims, all debates will be held in British Parliamentary (BP) Format.</li><li>The rules will be explained to the finalists at the venue.</li><li>The speakers will be judged on manner, matter, and method.]]></string>
    <string name="shipwreck_cove_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><h4>Preliminary Round</h4><ol><li>A hypothetical scenario presented depicts a ship full of famous personalities that is wrecked and sinking. The judges (captains) have limited life jackets remaining for the passengers.</li><li>A personality is allotted to each contestant ONE minute before speaking, for preparation.</li><li>Participants must convince the captains as to why they deserve to be saved (while sticking to their character). The speaking time is TWO minutes.</li><li>Judging criteria include wit, delivery, and character portrayal.</li><li>Witty innuendoes will earn you bonus points.</li></ol><h4>Final Round</h4><ol><li>All the rules of the preliminary round apply to the final round.</li><li>An additional reply session will take place, where each contestant must convince the judges why the other passengers deserve to drown.</li></ol>]]></string>
    <string name="the_legend_of_sir_speak_a_lot_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><ol><li>The English Poetry Slam and the English Elocution will be judged as distinct events. Participants can take part in either one or both of these events.</li><li>The participants will be required to compose an original poem for the Poetry Slam and an original speech for the Elocution.</li><li>The participants have the freedom to choose a theme of their choice for both events. The maximum time for recitation in both events is Five minutes.</li><li>Participants will be judged on the basis of their content and delivery.</li><li>Any plagiarism will result in immediate disqualification.</li><li>Decisions taken by the judges are final and binding.</li></ol>]]></string>
    <string name="a_jesters_court_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><ol><li>The stage is all yours for FIVE minutes.</li><li>Any plagiarism will lead to immediate disqualification.</li><li>Any form of pre-recorded music is not allowed during the performance.</li><li>Props are allowed but carry no point. Participants can use it to enhance theperformance.</li><li>Visual aids (slides/videos/pictures) are not to be used.</li><li>Any form of mono acting will lead to deduction of marks.</li><li>The performance can be in Hindi or English or both.</li><li>Obscenity is left to judges’ discretion.</li></ol>]]></string>
    <string name="vaad_vivaad_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><h4>Preliminary Round</h4><ol><li>It is an extempore event, so the topics will be provided on the spot, and each participant shall be given TWO minutes to prepare.</li><li>The participants can choose their stance and speak for a maximum of THREE minutes.</li><li>Judging criteria include content, organization and delivery.</li><li>The decision of the judges is final and profanity will be penalized with disqualification. The judges have final authority on determining the extent of profanity.</li></ol><h4>Final Round</h4><p>The rules will be explained to the finalists at the venue.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="alfaaz_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><ol><li>Contestants can recite any self-composed poetry on any topic, with a maximum peaking time of 5 minutes.</li><li>Participants will be judged on their content and delivery. Any plagiarism will result in disqualification</li></ol>]]></string>
    <string name="ashubhashan_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><h4>Preliminary Round</h4><ol><li>A personality is allotted to each contestant ONE minute before speaking, for preparation.</li><li>Participants must deliver a witty impromptu speech in Hindi, while sticking to their character. The speaking time is TWO minutes.</li><li>Judging criteria include wit, delivery, and character portrayal.</li><li>Witty innuendoes will earn you bonus points.</li></ol><h4>Final Round</h4><p>The rules will be explained to the finalists at the venue.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="whats_the_word_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><ol><li>Contestants compete in teams of 2.</li><li>A questionnaire containing various word puzzles and riddles is presented.</li><li>Teams have 1 hour to solve all the questions.</li></ol>]]></string>
    <string name="hinkhoj_rules"><![CDATA[<style>ol,ul{padding-left:20px;text-align:justify;}p{text-align: justify;}</style><ol><li>A presentation  containing various word puzzles, general Hindi literature related questions and riddles will be presented.</li><li>More rules will be explained on the spot.</li></ol>]]></string>
    <string name="title_activity_registration">Register</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="title_activity_gallery">GalleryActivity</string>
    <!--
    This string is used for square devices and overridden by hello_world in
    values-round/strings.xml for round devices.
    -->
    <string name="hello_world">Hello Square World!</string>

    <!-- Srings related to faq questions -->


    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
</resources>